# henry brown

Alexander Street, Toronto, Ontario | 800-233-9910 henrybrown0814@gmail.com

# **Summary**

Goal-oriented Web Developer brings strong commitment to collaboration and solutions-oriented problem-solving. Use various web design packages to develop custom-crafted, customer-focused websites and designs. Committed to high standards of user experience, usability and speed over more than 7 years for multiple users. Lends detailed knowledge of SEO to increase visibility. Logical and results-driven Web Developer dedicated to building and optimizing user-focused websites for customers with various business objectives. Judicious and creative when crafting effective websites, apps and platforms to propel competitive advantage and revenue growth. Technically proficient and analytical problem solver with calm and focused demeanor.

## Experience

## Front End Developer

### ELEKS | Ontario, Toronto

## Senior Front End Developer | 01/2021 - Present

ELEKS service include custom software development, product design, quality assurance, R&D, smart teams and support and maintenance services. Talent members have a competition on ELEKS to get more votes from the customers It is a marketing website for customers who love to see and get more talented photos I worked on the competition features on the project and there built many functionalities such as Real-Time communication, Competition,

## Opextel LLC | Ontario, Toronto

## Front End Developer | 02/2020 - 01/2021

accompanyingOpenXcell provide services in software conceptualization & design, software product development, software product re-engineering, software maintenance All of the social media and collaboration tools are integrated into the project, also auto sending invoice to the clients with detailed information is completely implemented to the project so many of the customers love to use this one There were 5 front end developers and 2 backend developers in the team and I was front end leader on that team.

- Attend to the childrens' basics needs, including feeding and bathroom acommpanying
- · Hire, onboard, and train new employees, including instructing on food safety, customer service standards, and operations

### Admios | Ontario, Toronto

#### Front-End Developer/Designer | 02/2018 - 02/2020

- Created custom AngularJS components for internal framework
- Translated design team's UX wireframes and mockups into responsive, interactive features, using HTML/CSS and JavaScript
- Translated design team's UX wireframes and mockups into responsive, interactive features, using HTML/CSS and JavaScript
- Assisted nurses with diagnostic procedures, treatments, and patient charting

## Light It | Ontario, Toronto

### Front End Leader | 01/2016 - 02/2018

Light IT provides innovative web and mobile software solutions for startups and enterprises. Hardscaping platform for homeowners and contractors Slo having a contractor's dashboard so that the contractors could work for our company

- Built trusted relationships with residents by getting to know them on a personal level and making their comfort a priority
- Troubleshoot network and production issues and perform root-cause analysis

## Skills

Javascript, CSS, React.js, C++, php

#### Education

## University of Toronto | Toronto, Ontario Computer Science | 01/2016

- · Currently completing courses in computer science, robotics and statistics
- · Majored in English Literature

## Languages

